Fastest draw in the North... kinda.
Gunless is a drama, action, comedy film directed by William Phillips.
American gunslinger Sean Rafferty—aka The Montana Kid—is unable to find someone to duel in a
Canadian town where no one understands the brutal code of the American Wild West.
Sean 'The Montana Kid' Rafferty, played by Paul Gross.
Jane Taylor, played by Sienna Guillory.
Jack Smith, played by Tyler Mane.
Ben Cutler, played by Callum Keith Rennie.
Corporal Jonathan Kent, played by Dustin Milligan.
Two Dogs, played by Graham Greene.
Gunless is a 2010 Canadian Western comedy film directed by
William Phillips and released by Alliance Films.
The film explores themes of blacksmith,
gunslinger, bounty hunter, duel, wild west.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.